Guide to the Willard Dickerman Straight papers, 1825-1925.
Straight, Willard Dickerman papers, 1825-1925.
- Visual Materials
  - Java People (commercial photographs)
    - People n.d. (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - United States Postcards
    - California n.d. (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - United States Postcards
    - New York n.d. (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - United States Postcards
    - South Carolina n.d. (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - United States Postcards
    - Virginia n.d. (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - United States Postcards
    - Yellowstone Natl. Park n.d. (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Canadian Postcards
    - Canada, British Columbia n.d. (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Mexican and Brazilian Postcards (annotated)
    - Mexico, Cuernavaca 1916, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Mexican and Brazilian Postcards (annotated)
    - Brazil, Rio de Janeiro 1916,n.d. (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - British Postcards
    - England n.d. (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - British Museum Indian Art
    - Art, Indian n.d. (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - British Museum Indian Art
    - British Museum, London, England n.d. (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Norwegian Postcards
    - Norway n.d. (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Italian Postcards
    - Art, Italian n.d. (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Italian Postcards
    - Italy n.d. (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Italian Postcards
    - Italy, Venice n.d. (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - French Postcards
    - France, Andelot 1914-1917 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - French Postcards
    - France, Ferte-Sous-Jouarre 1914-1917 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - French Postcards
    - France, Montreuil-Aux-Lions 1914-1917 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - French Postcards
    - France, Nice 1914-1917 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Old Langres
    - France, Langres n.d. (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Old Langres
    - France, Langres n.d. (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Langres
    - France, Langres n.d. (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Langres
    - Straight, Willard D. n.d. (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Langres
    - France, Langres n.d. (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - World War I
    - American Expeditionary Forces 1914-1918 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - World War I
    - France, Luneville 1914-1918 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - World War I
    - France, Nancy 1914-1918 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - World War I
    - World War I 1914-1918 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - World War I in Lorraine
    - France, Lorraine 1914-1918 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - World War I in Lorraine
    - France, Luneville 1914-1918 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - World War I in Lorraine
    - World War I 1914-1918 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Luneville before World War I
    - France, Luneville 1914c. (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Nancy
    - France, Nancy 1914c. (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Java and Johor
    - People 1910 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Java and Johor
    - Java 1910c. (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Java and Johor
    - Johor 1910c. (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Luneville before World War I
    - France, Luneville 1914c. (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - People of Java
    - People 1910 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - People of Java
    - Java 1910c. (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - People of Java
    - People 1910 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - People of Java
    - Java 1910c. (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Published Guides and Souvenir Views
    - France n.d. (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Published Guides and Souvenir Views
    - France, Langres n.d. (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Japanese People
    - People 1905 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Japanese People
    - Japan 1905c. (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Japanese Art
    - Art, Japan 1905 c. (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Japanese Art
    - Japan 1905c. (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Japanese Scenes
    - Japan 1905c. (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Japanes Scenes
    - Japan 1905c. (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Japanese Scenes
    - Japan 1905c. (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Korean Scenes
    - Korea 1904c. (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Korean Scenes
    - Korea 1904c. (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Korean Scenes
    - Korea 1904c. (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Korean Women and Village Scenes
    - People 1904 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Korean Women and Village Scenes
    - Korea 1904c. (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Korean Occupations
    - People 1904 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Korean Occupations
    - Korea 1904c. (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Portraits of Korean People
    - People 1904 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Portraits of Korean People
    - Dress 1904c. (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Portraits of Korean People
    - Korea 1904c. (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Portraits of Korean People
    - People 1904 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Portraits of Korean People
    - Dress 1904c. (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Portraits of Korean People
    - Korea 1904c. (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Chinese Revolution
    - China, Hankow 1912c. (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Chinese Revolution
    - China, Hupeb 1912c. (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Summer Palace (annotated)
    - China, Peking 1910c. (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Summer Palace (annotated)
    - Summer Palace n.d. (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Peking Landmarks
    - Ceremonies 1910c. (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Peking Landmarks
    - China, Peking 1910c. (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Peking Landmarks
    - Temples 1910c. (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Peking Landmarks
    - Winter Palace 1910c. (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Transportation (annotated)
    - China, Peking 1910c. (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Harbin
    - China, Manchuria, Harbin 1905c. (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Harbin
    - Russo-Japanese War 1905c. (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - China, Canton 1910c. (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Hong Kong, Macao
    - Hong Kong 1910c. (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Hong Kong, Macao
    - Macao 1910c. (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Chinese People and Scenes (annotated)
    - People 1910 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Chinese People and Scenes (annotated)
    - China, Hankow 1910c. (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Chinese People and Scenes (annotated)
    - Great Wall 1910c. (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Ming Tombs
    - Ming Tombs 1910c. (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Ming Tombs (annotated)
    - China 1910c. (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - China Scenes (annotated)
    - China n.d. (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - China Scenes (annotated)
    - Yangtze River n.d. (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Published Guides and Souvenir Views
    - Canada n.d. (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Published Guides and Souvenir Views
    - Massachusetts, Cape Cod n.d. (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Published Guides and Souvenir Views
    - Russia, Habarovsk n.d. (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Chinese Scenes (mounted enlargements)
    - Agriculture n.d. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Scenes (mounted enlargements)
    - Camel Caravans n.d. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Scenes (mounted enlargements)
    - Children n.d. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Scenes (mounted enlargements)
    - China n.d. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Scenes (mounted enlargements)
    - Dress n.d. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Scenes (mounted enlargements)
    - Government Officials n.d. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Scenes (mounted enlargements)
    - Transportation, Camel Caravans n.d. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Scenes (mounted enlargements)
    - Transportation, Carts n.d. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Scenes (mounted enlargements)
    - Camel Caravans n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Chinese Scenes (mounted enlargements)
    - China, Peking n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Chinese Scenes (mounted enlargements)
    - Great Wall n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Chinese Scenes (mounted enlargements)
    - Summer Palace n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Chinese Scenes (mounted enlargements)
    - Transportation, Camel Caravans n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Portraits (mounted enlargements)
    - Davison, Henry P. 1910 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Portraits (mounted enlargements)
    - People, Identified Individuals 1910 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Portraits (mounted enlargements)
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Japanese 1910 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Portraits (mounted enlargements)
    - Pirie MacDonald, New York, New York 1910 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Portraits (mounted enlargements)
    - Portraits 1910 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Portraits (mounted enlargements)
    - C.E. Lemunyon, Peking and Tientsin, China 1910c. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Portraits (mounted enlargements)
    - China, Manchuria 1910c. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Portraits (mounted enlargements)
    - Dress 1910c. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Portraits (mounted enlargements)
    - Japan 1910c. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Portraits (mounted enlargements)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1910c. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Portraits (mounted enlargements)
    - Suzuki, Japan 1910c. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Portraits (mounted enlargements)
    - Women 1910c. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Group Portraits
    - American Group 1904, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Group Portraits
    - Calhoun, William J. 1904-1911 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Group Portraits
    - Casenave, Maurice 1904-1911 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Group Portraits (mounted)
    - Gatrell, Thomas J. 1904, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Group Portraits (mounted)
    - Jordan, John N. 1904, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Group Portraits (mounted)
    - Russo-Japanese War 1904, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Group Portraits (mounted)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1904, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Group Portraits (mounted)
    - Tsai Tze 1904, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Group Portraits (mounted)
    - Chinese Currency and Industrial Development Loan 1904-1911 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Group Portraits (mounted)
    - Collins, Robert M. 1904-1911 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Group Portraits (mounted)
    - People, Identified Groups 1904-1911 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Group Portraits (mounted)
    - Portraits 1904-1911 (Box 75, Folder 4)